(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D SHOWCASE #RatIdol3D
September 30 20:00 (PDT)
October 1 05:00 (CEST) 12:00 (JST)
Welcome to the Fun Zone!
Located in God knows where...
...we present to you a place where all your wildest dreams can become your reality.
A place where you make the rules.
You can be anyone.
You can do anything.
A theme park made to accommodate just you.
We have state-of-the-art rides...
...food, and entertainment for all of our guests.
You'll never want to leave.
So come on down to the Fun Zone!
For the fun has only just begun!
WHAT'S UP EVERYONE!!
IT'S BAE!!
From... I can't feel my head, oh my god.
みんなようこそ3Dお披露目！！
Everyone, welcome to my 3D showcase!!
Hi! Ahahaha!
What's up everyone!
It's me!
Hello, hello, I see you all! Oh my god, hello!
It's Bae from Hololive English!
Welcome to my 3D showcase!
Hello, hello! There's so many of you! Hello!
Yes, welcome to the Fun Zone!
Welcome to my cage! Isn't my cage brilliant?
It's more of like a summer getaway kind of vacation thing.
Look, do you see me? Look! Ha!
Look at this! Haha!
What's up, what's up, hi everyone, what's up! Isn't this so cool?
Huuh... Oh am I already out of breath? It's like only the beginning, but it's fine!
I am here and I'm so happy that we finally got here!
Make sure you use the hashtag! Yay!
#RatIdol3D
I want to see all of your screenshots, all of your comments, and let's get it trending, guys! Let's go!
いや～本当に、あ、あの、楽しみにしてたので、はい！
Man, I was really, uh, looking forward to this, so yeah!
どうぞ、ハッシュタグ使ってください。はい。
Please, use the hashtag. Yes.
で！
And!
Well... Um... Speaking of 3D...
...there's a very special friend, and I couldn't have done this without him, so...
...I just wanted to quickly introduce my dearest friend...
...and the one who's really in charge of everything. Squeaks.
Lord Squeaks has arrived, everybody.
LORD SQUEAKSY!!
可愛いっしょ？可愛いでしょ？
Isn't he cute? He's cute, right?
Squeaks, Squeaks has joined the party! Heehee!
Hi everyone! Oh my god, chat's going so quick. Hello!
Yeet! I'm not gonna yeet. No.
I'm gonna be nice to Mr. Squeaks today because he's done a lot for me.
I'm gonna put you right here.
Well, it is obviously mandatory when it comes to 3D...
...we have so much planned today.
Literally, I'm on a time... I'm on a really big time limit.
Okay, so you have one minute. Everyone, you have one minute...
...to give me all the poses that you want me to do.
I'm gonna do as much as I can. I'm gonna read them in the chat.
You have one minute. Ready? Time starts now!
Waiting. The time is ticking.
JoJo pose! Hai! Next!
JoJo pose! Okay! Next!
Splits! Do splits! Okay!
I don't know how far I can go, this is as far as I can...
Aaaaah! Dada-da-da!
Next!
Naruto run!
Dogeza! I already did the Dogeza! Next!
Deep repose?
Mermaid pose?
Like...
...IRyS? Is that what she did?
Class 5 Hurricane! Waaaaa!
Next! You have 10 seconds.
Oh, the worm!
I'm gonna break my entire body...
...and this show's gonna be cancelled if I do the worm.
Cartwheel please!
You gotta dab?
Dab. There we go.
Anyway, thank you, that was your minute.
I hope you guys are satisfied with that.
I tried my best.
Thank you management, thank you. Alright!
Today we have so many things prepared.
I've got a lot of songs...
...maybe some dances...
...and...
...I've got a game.
My brain kind of... I've had so much caffeine, guys, my brain is like not working.
We have a game...
...and I hope you're ready to have some fun!
But for a game, I need people to play games with.
Because unless, you know, as you can see...
...I'm kind of alone here in my cage...
...so I really need some friends to play with.
So... oh! What's that? Wait, what?
I think some people are entering the gates of the Fun Zone!
What? Guess who could they be? I wonder.
なんか、来た、方、いらっしゃるんじゃないんですか？
I think some people have arrived!
Dada-da-da!
You ready to find out? Let's go!
Now Loading
Yeeeah!
My guests are here!
ま、ま、ま、自己紹介お願いします！
P-p-p-please introduce yourselves!
Please introduce yourself! Hi!
最初は...
First is...
Hi!
皆、こんそらー！Hello everyone!
Hello everyone! Hello everyone!
I'm ホロライブJPメンバー、ときのそら！
I'm Hololive JP member, Tokino Sora!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
そして...
And then...
Next! Next! Oh, over here? Okay.
はい、皆さん、こんこんきつね！
Hi, everyone! Kon-Kon-Kitsune!
ホロライブフォックス、白上フブキです。Hi friends!
Hololive Fox, I'm Shirakami Fubuki. Hi friends!
Hi friends!
そして...
And then...
Hi! My name is Subaru Oozora!
I belong to Hololive 2nd Generation!
Today, I will be...
Yeah! Yeeeah!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
Welcome to the Fun Zone!
The Fun Zone! Welcome!
そうですよね。
That's right.
来てくれてありがとう！
Thanks for coming!
なんか、すごいねここね！
This place is amazing, isn't it!
すごい！
Amazing!
Ehe, ehe, ehe!
3Dの、お祝いとしてね、あの...
As a 3D celebration, you know...
やっぱりゲームを用意しました。
I've prepared a game after all.
I prepared a board game to celebrate, you know, 3D...
...and so I can have fun with my daiji na senpai.
...and so I can have fun with my dear seniors.
So we're gonna play a game together.
うわっ！見て！
Whoa! Look!
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
So we have game pieces.
Everyone has a mascot that will be driving along the board in their own go-karts.
Driving! Whoa! Amazing!
動いてる！
They're moving!
マスコット、マスコット！可愛い！
Mascots, mascots! Cute!
So, for the game, I'm gonna explain the rules... first...
まずルール説明します。
First, I'll explain the rules.
おお、サイコロ！
Oh, a dice!
おお、来た。
Oh, it's here.
でかっ！でかいですよね、これ！
It's huge! This is huge, isn't it?
でかーい！
It's huge!
We have a dice!
重い、重い、重い！
It's heavy, heavy, heavy!
Big dice!
誰が振る？
Who's going to roll it?
Big dice! Big dice!
ルール説明、はい！
Rule explanation, let's go!
So we'll be rolling this dice and advancing towards the finish line...
...while we collect cheese. (Everyone) Cheese!
You can collect cheese by playing mini-games or by completing a lap...
...and when the game is over, the player with the most pieces of cheese is the winner.
ほう、なるほど！チーズ！
Oh, I see! Cheese!
フブキ、そら、スバル、ねえ。
Fubuki, Sora, Subaru, hey.
話聞いてません。
You guys aren't listening.
子供たちがはしゃぎすぎてて。
The kids are way too excited.
And whoever has the fewest pieces of cheese, the least amount of cheese...
...has to do a punishment challenge!
罰ゲーム！罰ゲーム！
Punishment game! Punishment game!
そう、みんなもね、頑張ってね。
So everyone, do your best, okay?
はい！おー！
Yes! Yay!
So we have four different spaces that you can land on.
The first space is called a Battle Space.
バトルスペース！バトルスペース！
Battle Space! Battle Space!
If you land on this space, you have to compete with the other players in a battle!
バトル！バトル！
Battle! Battle!
And the number of players will change depending on what kind of game it is.
Second kind of space is a Baelz Challenge Space!
ベールズチャレンジ！
Baelz Challenge!
このスペースは、僕とチャレンジ！
On this space, a challenge with me!
You'll be competing against me.
The winner will gain two pieces of cheese, loser will lose two pieces of cheese.
おお！なるほど！
Oh! I see!
Next space is Cheese Space!
チーズスペース！
Cheese Space!
Very simple, if you land on a blue cheese space, you gain one piece of cheese.
If you land on a red cheese space, you lose one piece of cheese.
えー！デンジャー！
What! Danger!
青色のチーズは+1チーズ、赤色はデンジャーですよ。
Blue cheese is +1 cheese, red is danger.
デンジャー！
Danger!
で、最後、and the most interesting space...
And finally, the most interesting space...
Chaos Space!
カオススペース！
No Chaos! Yes Chaos! Yes Chaos!
嘘だろ！？カオス！？
Are you kidding me!? Chaos!?
嘘だろ、ノー！
No way, no!
I'm so excited to see someone land on this because...
I have no idea what will happen.
このカオススペース、何が起こるか全然わからない。
I have no idea what will happen in this Chaos Space.
なんでだよ！用意したついでに！
Why not! Even though you prepared it!
いやいや、これこそ楽しさですよ。
No no, this is the fun of it.
なるほどね。
I see.
まあ、早速、オーダーを決めましょう。
Well then, let's decide the order right away.
オーダー！ダイスオーダー！
Order! Dice order!
We have to decide the turn, so...
最初は、そら先輩。オッケー！
First, Sora-senpai. Okay!
二番、フブキ先輩。オッケー！
Second, Fubuki-senpai. Okay!
次は、スバル先輩。
Next, Subaru-senpai.
で最後は、僕。オッケー！
And finally, me. Okay!
みんな準備いいですか？
Is everyone ready?
オッケー！イエーイ！
Okay! Yay!
Time to play Rat Trap!
はい、そら先輩どうぞ。
Okay, Sora-senpai, go ahead.
ぬるっと始まりましたね。そうですね。
It started so suddenly. Yeah.
スタート！レッツゴー！
Start! Let's go!
おお！1！
Oh! 1!
1マス！
1 space!
ドンマイ！どんまいですね。
Don't mind! Don't mind.
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go go go!
おー！行きますよー。
Oh! Here I go.
可愛いですね。ドライビング。行きます行きます。
How cute. Driving. Go, go, go.
1はどんなスペースかな？何があるんですか？
What kind of space is 1? What's on it?
おお、バトル！バトルスペース！
Oh, battle! Battle space!
バトル！ワット・バトル？
Battle! What battle?
So we have the first mini-game.
The first mini-game is Pose and a Phrase... (Explaining the rules)
なるほど！
I see!
So, そら先輩 versus フブキ先輩。
So, Sora-senpai versus Fubuki-senpai.
おー！
Ooh!
Make a pose, say a one-liner...
Select a topic.
どっちに行く？クール、キュート、セクシー。
Which one? Cool, cute, or sexy?
アングリー。
Angry.
で、どっちがもっと上手く表情できるか。
And who can make a better expression.
得意な分野かな、キューティーとか。
My specialty, maybe? Like cutie?
キュートかクールか、セクシー、アングリー。
Cute, cool, sexy, or angry?
どれがいいかな？そらちゃんが決めて。
Which one? You decide, Sora-chan.
セクシー！セクシー！
Sexy! Sexy!
同じトピックで。表情対決！
With the same topic. Expression battle!
セクシー対決！
Sexy showdown!
レッツゴー！そらセクシー！
Let's go! Sora sexy!
言葉も？セリフも？
Words too? Lines too?
先輩、セリフも。そらちゃん。
Senpai, lines too. Sora-chan.
行けるか？思い切りセクシーでいいのか？
Can you do it? Are you ready for full sexy?
もう始まってる、もう始まってるよ。
It's already started, it's already started!
いくよ！3、2、1、スタート。
Here I go! 3, 2, 1, start.
君、一緒に遊ばない？
Hey, won't you play with me?
おおー！ドキドキ！
Ooh! Heart-pounding!
ネクスト！
Next!
フブキ先輩。セクシーですよ。
Fubuki-senpai. It's your turn for sexy.
フブキ・セクシー・チャレンジ！
Fubuki Sexy Challenge!
Go!
セクシー...
Sexy...
え、これでいいのかな？
Eh, is this okay?
セクシー！
Sexy!
待って、
Wait,
どっち、どっち、どっちがいい？
which one, which one, which one is better?
どっちがいい？
Which one?
どっち？
ど、ど、ど、どっち？
Wh-wh-wh-which one?
I recommend Sora.
いや、すみません、フブキもいますよ。
No, excuse me, Fubuki is here too.
勝った！ありがとうございます！
I won! Thank you very much!
いえーい、勝った！
Yay, I won!
ナイス！
Nice!
Fubuki is a little shy.
あ、可愛すぎた。
Ah, she was too cute.
あ、キュートだった。
Ah, she was cute.
そうか、キュートだったか。
I see, she was cute.
おめでとう。
Congratulations.
でも次は進めるんだね、よかった。
But we can move forward next, good.
なるほど。
I see.
よし、次！
Okay, next!
行くか、よし。
Let's go, alright.
Let's go!
よし、チーズマスに止まりたい。
Alright, I want to stop on a cheese space.
カモン、チーズ！
Come on, cheese!
ノーチーズ！
No cheese!
６！６！６！
Six! Six! Six!
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go, go, go!
行け、フブラ！
Go, Fubura!
フブラでけえ！
Fubura is huge!
これ大丈夫か？すごいな、おい。
Is this okay? It's amazing.
行け行け行け、フブラ！
Go, go, go, Fubura!
どんどん、どんどん見てまいりますが、すごいすごい。
We keep looking at her, amazing, amazing.
え、どこまで行くの？
Eh, how far is she going?
よし、次はそらだ！カモン、チーズ！
Alright, next is Sora! Come on, cheese!
カモン、チーズ！
Come on, cheese!
Cheese Space
でもでもでも、チーズ？
But, but, but, cheese?
レッドかブルーどっちか。
Red or Blue, which one?
どっち？
Which one?
これはレッド... あ、ブルー！
This is red... ah, blue!
Blue cheese
1 cheese won
ブルー！やったー、ブルー！
Blue! Yay, blue!
やったー！１チーズ獲得！
Yay! One cheese gained!
おめでとう、ブルーチーズ。やったね。
Congratulations, blue cheese. We did it.
いいなー。
That's nice.
よし、次は私！
Alright, next is me!
私がチーズをゲット。カオス空間！
I'll get the cheese! Chaos Space!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
ちょっと待ってください。
Please wait a moment.
カオス！カオス！カオス！
Chaos! Chaos! Chaos!
カオス！
Chaos!
カオス！カオス！カオス！
Chaos! Chaos! Chaos!
はい、何ですか？
Yes, what is it?
何ですか？
What is it?
Baelz Challenge Space
ベールズチャレンジ！
Baelz Challenge!
カモン、ベールズ。負けませんよ。
Come on, Baelz. I won't lose.
なるほどね、ベールズチャレンジ。
I see, Baelz Challenge.
Freestyle Dance Battle
フリースタイル・ダンスバトル。フリースタイル・ダンス。
Freestyle Dance Battle. Freestyle dance.
ちょっと待ってよ。これ、ちょっとまずいよ。
Wait a minute. This is a bit bad.
フリースタイル・ダンス。やばい。
Freestyle dance. This is crazy.
あ、音楽があるみたいで。
Ah, there seems to be music.
セクシーダンス、行きましょうか。
Let's go for a sexy dance.
じゃあ、まず音楽お願いします。
Then, first, music please.
バカおしゃれじゃん。おしゃれやんけ。
It's so cool. How stylish.
これに合わせて２０秒？
Twenty seconds to this?
むずすぎるでしょ。
That's way too hard.
Freestyle dance, music!
ベールズ、フリースタイル全然できないよ。マジでフリースタイルできない。
Baelz, I can't do freestyle at all. Seriously, I can't.
じゃあ、これはでも一緒に踊ってもいいんじゃない？一緒に踊ろう！
Well then, maybe it's okay to dance together? Let's dance together!
Together danceしよう。一緒にダンスして。
Let's do a together dance. Let's dance together.
そういうやつ、コンボコンボ！
One of those, combo combo!
OK、OK。
OK, OK.
で、白上とそらちゃんが、どっちのダンスが魅力的だったかね、二人が勝者を決めます。
And Fubuki and Sora-chan will decide whose dance was more charming. You two decide the winner.
はい、じゃあ行きます。音楽お願いします！
Okay, here we go. Music, please!
あ、どっちが続けるのか？
Ah, which one is continuing?
ちょっと正面向いてやりなよ。
Hey, face the front!
二人で一緒に。
Both of you together.
これはちょっと too difficult チャレンジだよね。
This was a bit of a too difficult challenge, wasn't it?
そうだよね。
Right.
そらちゃん、どうだった、これ？
Sora-chan, what did you think of this?
一緒に踊っちゃってるんだよね、でも。
But they ended up dancing together.
ちょっと、これはもう勝負にならなかったということで。
Wait, this didn't even turn into a match.
二人とも負けだよ！
You both lose!
ねえ、そらちゃん、これ。チーズまた戻ってる。
Right, Sora-chan? The cheese is going back.
ドローだね。
It's a draw.
マイナス２チーズ！！
Minus 2 cheese!!
え、ねえ、マイナス２！？
Eh, what, minus 2!?
僕らのせいじゃないですよ！あんなに楽しく踊ったのに。
It's not our fault! We had so much fun dancing.
あんなに楽しかったのに、負けたよ。ということで、チーズの借金ですか？
Even though it was so fun, we lost. So, it's a cheese debt?
チーズ借金！チーズ借金！
Cheese debt! Cheese debt!
マイナス２チーズ。
Minus 2 cheese.
はい、次は僕ですね。
Alright, next is me.
まさかのマイナス確定。
An unexpected guaranteed minus.
マイナスってね。２期生、ゴー！
Minus, huh. Gen 2, go!
５！５！５！
Five! Five! Five!
みんな違うマスに止まってる。
Everyone stopped on different spaces.
本当だ、何マスかな？
True, which space is it?
カオス！
Chaos!
Chaos! Chaos! Chaos! Chaos!
I'm scared!
何もさ...
I have no idea...
Chaos Space
カオススペース！
Chaos Space!
待って、待って、待って。ちょっと待って、ルールを！
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on, the rule!
Hamster wheel!
Hamster Wheel
You must keep running on a hamster wheel
until the next person ends their turn
何て言うんだっけ？ ホイール？
What was it called? Wheel?
ハムスターホイール！
Hamster wheel!
ランニングホイール！
Running wheel!
ランニングホイール
次の人のターンが終わるまで
ランニングホイールで走り続ける
Running Wheel
Keep running on the running wheel
until the next person's turn ends
次の人のターンが終わるまで
ランニングホイールで走り続ける。
Keep running on the hamster wheel
until the next person's turn ends.
ララララララ！
Ra-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra!
You must keep on running! Hamster wheel!
I have to keep running on the hamster wheel
until the next person's turn ends!
ちょっと待って。ハ！
Hold on. Ha!
ちょっと待って。これ私の3D、
3Dお披露目配信なんですけど。
Wait a minute. This is my 3D,
3D debut stream, though.
ちょっと待って、スタッフさん！
Hold on, staff-san!
Don't worry!
じゃあ、ハコスちゃんは
次のそらちゃんの番が終わるまで走っててください。
Okay, Baelz, keep running
until Sora-chan's turn is over.
私はゆっくりやればいいってこと？
So I should just take my time?
そうそうそう！ そら先輩、愛してる！
Yes, yes, yes! Sora-senpai, I love you!
早めに、行きます！ スタート！
I'll go fast! Start!
Let's go!
ハヤ！
So fast!
え、すごい速い！
Whoa, that's really fast!
よし、そらちゃん！
時間はいっぱいあるから大丈夫！
Okay, Sora! We have plenty of time, so it's fine!
そら先輩、愛してる。お願いします。
Sora-senpai, I love you. Please.
うわー！
Whoa!
ファイブ！ ファイブ！
Five! Five!
そら先輩、愛してるー！
Sora-senpai, I love you!
ララララララ...
Ra-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra...
あ、あそこに。あ、追い越していく。
Oh, over there. Oh, she's passing.
うわー！
Whoa!
さあ、何になりますかね。
Now, what will it be?
むしろそらちゃんも一緒に走ってほしいな、なんなら。
I actually want Sora-chan to run with her too.
チーズ来い！ チーズ来い！
Cheese, come on! Cheese, come on!
何スペース？
What space?
チーズ！
Cheese!
Cheese Space
レッドオアブルー？ レッドオアブルー？
Red or blue? Red or blue?
ブルーチーズ！
Blue cheese!
Blue cheese
1 cheese won
青色チーズ
1チーズ獲得
Blue cheese
1 cheese won
お！ ワンチーズ！
Oh! One cheese!
おめでとう、チーズ！
Congratulations on the cheese!
ナイス、そらちゃん！ やったー！
Nice, Sora-chan! Yay!
はい、じゃあここでハコスちゃん、終わっていいよ！
Okay, Baelz-chan, you can stop now!
ナイスファイト！ 降りておいで、降りておいで。
Nice fight! Come on down, come on down.
ストップ、ザ、ホイール！
Stop the wheel!
ヘイ、ハコス！ インタビュータイム！ インタビュータイム！
Hey, Baelz! Interview time! Interview time!
今の気持ちは？
What are your feelings right now?
ナマ...
Numb...
ナマ？
Numb?
さあ次！ 次はナイスファイト！
Next! Next, nice fight!
行くぞ！ Let's go!
Going! Let's go!
うわー！ 5！
Whoa! Five!
一緒の場所か？ 一緒かな？
The same place? Is it the same?
ってことはチーズでは？
Does that mean cheese?
バトルスペース！ バトル！
Battle Space! Battle!
Battle Space
あ、白上とのバトルかじゃあ。そうですよね。
Oh, so a battle with Shirakami. Right.
なんですか？ ジェスチャー！
What is it? Charades!
Charades
- Have other players guess all the phrases in time
- Total of 3 phrases
ジェスチャーゲーム！ オッケー。
Charades game! Okay.
なるほど。30秒。
I see. 30 seconds.
ジェスチャーゲーム
・他3人がジェスチャーを当てる
・制限時間30秒以内に3つ出来たらクリア
Charades game
- The other 3 guess the gestures
- Clear if 3 are done within the 30-second time limit
白上が出したやつに、他の3人が
ジェスチャー当ててもらう感じね。
The other three will have to
guess the charades that Fubuki does.
オッケー、オッケー。いけるんじゃないか？
Okay, okay. We can do this, right?
30秒以内にみんなに当ててもらわなきゃいけないんだね。
We have to have everyone guess them within 30 seconds.
So three in 30 seconds. Okay.
3つ連続、あ、じゃあ3つ。
Three in a row, oh, okay, three.
それと、それと、それ。
That, and that, and that.
あ、オッケー、オッケー。
Oh, okay, okay.
オッケー、オッケー。いける、いける！
Okay, okay. We can do it!
オッケーですか？ じゃあ、こっち向いたほうがいいかな？
Are you ready? Should I face this way?
じゃあみんな書いてね。
Okay everyone, write it down.
横、あ、こっちか。こっち向いた。オッケー、オッケー。
Side, oh, this way. Facing here. Okay, okay.
用意、スタート！
Ready, start!
コアラ！
Koala!
オッケー！ 次！
Correct! Next!
Question 1
コアラ
Koala
Question 1
マッスル！ ボディビル！
Muscle! Bodybuilding!
Question 2
ボディビル
Bodybuilding
Question 2
オッケー！
Correct!
最後の最後！
The very last one!
シャイ？ 違う。トイレ！ トイレ！
Shy? No. Toilet! Toilet!
トイレ行きたい人！ トイレ！
Needing the toilet! Toilet!
流す！ おしっこ！
Flush! Pee!
Question 3
トイレに行く人
People going to the restroom
Question 3
トイレに行く人！
People going to the restroom!
オッケー！
Correct!
オッケー！ 終了！ すごーい！
Okay! Finished! Amazing!
分かりやすかった！ 分かりやすかった！
That was easy to understand! It was clear!
白上先輩もすごい！
Fubuki-senpai is amazing too!
ってことで、1進めます！ 1！ やったー！
With that, move forward one! One! Yay!
おめでとう！ 1！
Congratulations! One!
次はスバちゃんの番！
Next is Subaru-chan's turn!
マイターン！ マイターン！ マイターン！
My turn! My turn! My turn!
行くぞ！
Going!
速い、速い、速い、速い！
Fast, fast, fast, fast!
2！ 2、2、2！
Two! Two, two, two!
ナイス！ どこ行くかな？
Nice! Where will it go?
カオス、カオス！
Chaos, chaos!
カオス！ カオス！
Chaos! Chaos!
Chaos Space
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
カオスやべーだろマジで。
Chaos is seriously crazy.
カオスの内容は…
The chaos content is...
Vegemite Challenge
ベジマイトを食べないと前に進むことができない。
You cannot advance any further until you eat Vegemite.
スバル先輩、ベジマ大好きだから。
Subaru-senpai, you love Vegemite, right?
やだ！食べたくないベジマイト！
No! I don't want to eat Vegemite!
レッツゴー！食べよ！
Let's go! Let's eat!
ということでベジマイト大好き？
So, do you love Vegemite?
I love Vegemite.
ベジマイトってどんなの？
What's Vegemite like?
Did you try Vegemite?
Smell it, smell it first.
二人ともまだ食べたことないんで。
Both of them haven't eaten it yet.
なんだろう…なんか…
What is it... it's like...
Tasty!
お、でもなんだろう。匂いだけだとそこまで。
Oh, but what is it? Just from the smell, it's not that bad.
Like a miso.
ミソ？
Miso?
It's a world-famous Vegemite.
すごい濃い。いただきます。
It's very strong. Let's eat.
It's not fair! 僕もベジマイト食べたい！
It's not fair! I want to eat Vegemite too!
Tasty!
美味しい！美味しい！
Delicious! Delicious!
休憩…休憩フードみたいな。
It's like... a snack break food.
いいな、ベジマイト食べてみたい。お腹空いた。
Nice, I want to try Vegemite. I'm hungry.
味噌汁だ味噌汁。Like a miso soup.
It's miso soup, miso soup. Like a miso soup.
You're making miso soup in your mouth.
さあ、次はハコスちゃん！いきます！
All right, next is Hakos-chan! Here I go!
ファイブ！ファイブ！
Five! Five!
さあ、次は…何が出るかな？
Now, next... what will it be?
What happens if I land on my land on my land on...
うわ、それどこまで行く？
Whoa, how far are you going?
どこまで…さあ、こちらのマスは？
How far... Now, what is this space?
何でしょうか？レッツゴー！
What is it? Let's go!
カオス！またカオス！
Chaos! Chaos again!
Surprise Warp
ちょっと待って！うわあ！
Wait a minute! Whoa!
ハプニングワープ！スタート位置に戻るとチーズが二つ減る。
Surprise Warp! Return to the start position and lose two cheeses.
待って、Here we go!
Wait, here we go!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
投石機じゃねーか！
It's a catapult!
ちょっと待って！ちょっと待って！ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
ギャアアア！サヨナラー！
Gyaaaa! Goodbye!
Goodbye Hakos! Bye-bye!
マイナス二つということは、元々マイナス二つだから…
Minus two means, since it was minus two to begin with...
マイナス四！うわあ！
Minus four! Whoa!
I'm at minus four cheese.
頑張って！やばい！
Good luck! That's bad!
やばい！マイナス…あ、一個ゲットしてるんだ。
Oh no! Minus... oh, I got one.
ああ、よかったよかった。
Oh, that's good.
Minus three. We're minus three.
じゃあ続いてそらちゃん！
Then, next is Sora-chan!
チーズ食べれないね。チーズ欲しい！
We can't eat cheese, can we? I want cheese!
I want cheese! Let's go! Let's go!
行けー！ファイブ！
Go! Five!
五がいっぱい出るね。そうね。
Lots of fives coming up. Yeah.
さあさあ、五。レッツゴー！
All right, five. Let's go!
あれ？あれ？おおー！
Wait? Huh? Ohhh!
チーズゲット！ゴール！
Cheese get! Goal!
チーズゲット！ナイス！
Cheese get! Nice!
一周したらですね、チーズゲットということで。このマスは貰えたってことで。
Once you complete a lap, you get a cheese. So you got this space.
おめでとう！サンキュー！
Congratulations! Thank you!
おめでとうセレブレーション！
Congratulatory celebration!
バトル！バトル！
Battle! Battle!
What's the battle this time?
さてさて、このバトルは？
Now, what is this battle?
Pose and a Phrase
ポーズで一言！そら先輩とフブキ先輩の対決になります。
Pose and a Phrase! It's a showdown between Sora-senpai and Fubuki-senpai.
I want to look very very angry Sora.
I want to look at a very, very angry Sora.
アングリーそら！アングリーフブキ！
Angry Sora! Angry Fubuki!
怒りそら先輩、怒りフブキ先輩、ベリーベリーアングリー！
Angry Sora-senpai, angry Fubuki-senpai, very very angry!
お題もね、意味の一言。
And the topic, just a short phrase.
おこ、おこ。いいんですか？
Angry, angry. Are you ready?
アングリーそら。よし！
Angry Sora. All right!
アングリーそら、3, 2, 1, Go!
Angry Sora, 3, 2, 1, Go!
本当にムカつく！
I'm really annoyed!
もうあんたは敵なんだから！
You're an enemy now!
うわあー！拍手！拍手！
Whoa! Applause! Applause!
Scary! Nice performance!
I am your friend.
よしよしよし…待って待って待って。
Okay okay okay... wait wait wait.
次はフブキ！フブキおこ、3, 2, 1, Go!
Next is Fubuki! Fubuki angry, 3, 2, 1, Go!
あのさ、請求額のこれ10万円って何？
Hey, what's this 100,000 yen charge?
また課金したの？何のガチャ引いたの？
Did you spend on microtransactions again? What gacha did you pull?
ねえ。良くないよそういうのはさ。ねえ。
Hey. That's not good, you know. Hey.
白上も回したいって言ったよね？何でそうやって白上の知らないところでガチャ引いちゃうわけ？
I told you I wanted to pull too, right? Why are you pulling gacha without me knowing?
お願い本当にさ…
Please, seriously...
ストップ！ストップ！大丈夫、大丈夫！
Stop! Stop! It's okay, it's okay!
キャラに入りすぎた。ちょっと待って、静かな怒りだったね。
I got too into character. Wait a minute, that was a quiet anger.
確かに、静かな怒り。怖かった。
True, a quiet anger. It was scary.
そうだよ、むつかしい。むつかしいね。
Yeah, it's hard. It's hard, isn't it?
むつかしい。バッシュ！
It's hard. Bash!
Sorry, Sora.
ちょっと、今回は空気がやばい。
Wait, the atmosphere is crazy this time.
やったー！ういー！
Yay! Whee!
本物の怒りだった
That was real rage.
やったー。じゃあ一番進めるー。えい！
Yay! I'm moving forward the most! Here!
これでチーズは...
With this, the cheese...
...スバルちゃんがゲットした。いぇーい
...Subaru-chan got it. Yay!
よし、じゃあ次かな
Alright, next then.
白上側で最後？もしかして
Is Shirakami's side the last one, maybe?
これで最後かな。じゃあ最後行きます。ラストターン！
This might be the last. I'll go then. Last turn!
2！ 2！
Two! Two!
ナイス2！
Nice two!
何来る？
What's coming?
バトルスペース！
Battle Space!
お、スバルちゃんとバトル？
Oh, battle with Subaru-chan?
バトル！何のバトル？
Battle! What kind of battle?
早口言葉！
Tongue Twisters!
早口言葉で戦います！
We'll fight with tongue twisters!
のぞむところだよ。オッケー
That's what I wanted. Okay.
It's over. It's over.
これでもう終わりですよ
It's all over with this.
罰としてチーズ1個
One cheese as a penalty.
I will beat you!
やばいやばいやばい
Crap, crap, crap.
一体何の早口言葉なのかな？
What kind of tongue twister is it?
オー！ What's it gonna be?
Oh! What's it gonna be?
神アニメハコス大興奮
God-tier anime Hakos is super excited.
フブキ先輩からでいいですか？
Can Fubuki-senpai go first?
じゃあ白上から行きましょうか
Then let's go with Shirakami first.
3回言うんですよね
You have to say it three times, right?
オッケー。3回ね
Okay. Three times.
Ready... Go!
神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮
God-tier anime Hakos is super excited (x3)
いぇーい！
Yay!
さすがさすが。はい、スバルちゃん
As expected. Now, Subaru-chan.
スバル先輩、3, 2, 1, Go!
Subaru-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮、神アニメハコス大興奮
God-tier anime Hakos is super excited (x3)
おおー！すごい！
Ohh! Amazing!
じゃあまだ次がありますからね
Well, there's more to come.
なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな
I couldn't write Katakana very well.
これは行けるっしょ
This one's doable.
フブキ先輩、3, 2, 1, Go!
Fubuki-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな
I couldn't write Katakana very well (x3)
すごーい！
Amazing!
フブちゃんってロボットなの？はやっ！
Is Fubu-chan a robot? So fast!
No robot. No robot.
Subaru-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな、なかなかカタカナ書けなかったな
I couldn't write Katakana very well (x3)
すごーい！
Amazing!
やばいぞこれ。なかなかやるやんけ、フブちゃん
This is bad. You're doing pretty well, Fubu-chan.
あのときのときのそら
Tokino Sora from that time.
Fubuki-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら
Tokino Sora from that time (x3)
すごい！ばっちりじゃん！
Amazing! Perfect!
Next, Subaru-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら、あのときのときのそら
Tokino Sora from that time (x3)
おおー！すごい！
Ohh! Amazing!
全然負けないぞ
She's not losing at all.
もっと難しいやつ出てこいや！
Bring on something harder!
炙りカルビ
Seared kalbi.
難しい
That's hard.
You try. 炙りカルビ、あ...
You try. Seared kalbi, seared kal...
あっ！そう。はい
Ah! Right. Okay.
Fubuki-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ
Seared kalbi, seared kalbi, seared kalbi
おおー！
Ohh!
大丈夫ですか？スバルちゃん。炙りカルビ
Are you okay, Subaru-chan? Seared kalbi.
Subaru-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ。よっしゃー！
Seared kalbi, seared kalbi, seared kalbi. All right!
もう一回連続で
One more time in a row.
5回言います。5回
Say it five times. Five times.
Fubuki-senpai, 3, 2, 1, Go!
炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ
Seared kalbi (x5)
おおー！すごい！
Ohh! Amazing!
頑張れ、スバル先輩！ 3, 2, 1, Go!
Good luck, Subaru-senpai! 3, 2, 1, Go!
炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ、炙りカルビ
Seared kalbi (x5)
すごーい！
Amazing!
炙りカルビ x5
Aburi Karubi x5
待って、待って、待って！
Wait, wait, wait!
負けです！二人とも負けです！
You lost! You both lost!
負けました...
We lost...
私たちが勝ちで！私たちが勝ち！
We won! We're the winners!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ずるいよ！
That's unfair!
これで二人とも負けということで...
So, since both of you lost...
GAME OVER!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いやもう、すごい。最後すごかった。
Wow, that was amazing. The end was incredible.
Crazy Battle. Crazy Round.
We are going to now announce the winner. 結果発表したいと思います！
We are going to now announce the winner. Time for the results!
The player who collected the most pieces of cheese is...
誰だ誰だ...
Who is it, who is it...
Fubuki-senpai!
You are the winner! And Sora-senpai also had...
...3 pieces!
We have a tie!
やったー！やったー！
We did it! We did it!
嘘だー！待ってタイム！
No way! Wait, time out!
The player who collected the fewest pieces of cheese is...
はい、僕です。
Yes, it's me.
罰ゲーム！罰ゲーム！罰ゲーム！
Punishment game! Punishment game! Punishment game!
罰ゲーム！罰ゲーム！ほら！
Punishment game! Punishment game! Come on!
悪いネズミは罰ゲームだって。
Bad rats get a punishment game.
What's a batsu game? I don't know what this batsu game is!
罰ゲーム！罰ゲーム！
Punishment game! Punishment game!
マネージャー様お願いします！カモン！
Manager-sama, please! Come on!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
え、でもどこ行っちゃったんだろう？
Wait, but where did she go?
怖い、怖い、怖い。 Scary, scary.
Scary, scary, scary. Scary, scary.
Help me! Hakos me! Help me!
Help me! It's me, Hakos! Help me!
あ、なんかあっちから声がする。
Oh, I hear a voice from over there.
Help me! That doesn't make any sense!
Why am I here? I shouldn't be here.
今日はね、ハコスちゃんのね、3Dお披露目だったと思うけど...
I thought today was Hakos-chan's 3D showcase, but...
このままじゃ動物園に... Zoo let's go!
She's going to the zoo at this rate... Zoo, let's go!
Let's go! Bye Hakos!
泣かないで、泣かないで！
Don't cry, don't cry!
I present cheese! Yes, cheese kure!
I present cheese! Yes, give me cheese!
チーズを... チーズ... チーズをください！
Cheese... Give me cheese, please!
No cheese! No cheese, Sora! No cheese!
チーズだめ！チーズだめ！
No cheese! No cheese!
まあということで、今日皆来てくれて本当にありがとう。
Anyway, thank you all so much for coming today.
こちらこそ！おりの中から...
Our pleasure! From inside the cage...
皆のね、感想を聞きたいんですけど...
I want to hear your thoughts, though...
Very, very sad scene ya.
そらちゃんから、今日どうでした？
Sora-chan, how was it today?
Yeah, tell everyone how do you feel?
I'm so very excited!
Excited game and... many asobeta...
The games were exciting and we got to play many [of them]...
...many playing game! I'm so happy!
...playing many games! I'm so happy!
Yeah! Congratulations! おめでとう！
Yeah! Congratulations!
3D おめでとう！すごかったね！
Congratulations on your 3D! It was amazing!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
それからあれだ、こよりちゃんのラボに送ろう。
And also, let's send her to Koyori-chan's lab.
こよりラボに。実験マウス！
To Koyori Lab. Experimental mouse!
Please no!
まあまあまあ。
Now, now.
今日はおこう。
Let's let it go for today.
白上も今日は楽しかったねー。
Shirakami also had a lot of fun today.
チーズいっぱい持って帰ります！
I'll take home lots of cheese!
ハコスちゃん、おめでとう！
Hakos-chan, congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、次スバルちゃん。
Okay, next, Subaru-chan.
Me too, me too! I'm very happy!
Because today is Hakos's 3D showcase!
3D Showcase. Showcase. (Showcase!)
Showcase. ハコショーケース。
Showcase. Hako-showcase.
これがお披露目だったのか。悲しい...
So this was the showcase. How sad...
Thank you so much for coming... 来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming! Thank you for coming!
ちょっと、これからも一応ライブするので。
Wait, I'll still be doing a live concert from now on.
ダンスも、このまま、運んでもらって...
And for the dances, please just carry me like this...
何の事だろうに... The next, the next, I have some songs I'm going to sing...
What even is this... Next, I have some songs to sing...
...and I'm going to perform, so I hope everyone, please continue watching.
皆も、まだまだ、盛り上がっていきましょう！
Everyone, let's keep the excitement going!
これから出ます。出ます。
I'm coming out now. Coming out.
頑張って！ハコス！
Good luck, Hakos!
Thank you! Rat Trap! Bye-bye!
Enjoy showcase! イェーイ！
Enjoy the showcase! Yay!
誰か助けてー！
Someone help me!
Now Loading
Baby, the rat is finally 3D!
Yeah, hi! Let's chu chu chu!
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, and we just play dice.
Baby, baby, there's no need to think twice, nani nani no!
Make your night, make your vibe, make your spotlight.
Get up from that hands up and let's roll your life.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Play dice!
Hey, hey! Bae, Bae! Hey, hey! Bae, Bae!
Baby, so simple, it's irrelevant,
everyone born on the order when you ripped and tumbled
but we have no time to complain 'cause I for sure can do it all over again.
If we can laugh it doesn't matter where or when.
BG to hammer, physics don't play the dice, so let's travel, search, and prize.
Be limits bound, rule the chance, 意味なんてなああい
Be limits bound, rule the chance, there's no meaning at all!
So we don't give a chu! 嫌なことソッコーミュート
So we don't give a chu! Immediately mute the bad things
So find something new, かたじけ、しっ、今、チュー
So find something new, grateful, shh, now, a kiss
No cage can trap this rat! Bae! No cage can trap this rat! Bae!
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, and we just play dice.
Down the stream, come on out, don't be too nice, nani nani no!
Follow your heart, follow your feels, so come and join the club.
Go and scream for you're the one that's finally 3D!
転がすダイスはそのままでいい
Keep the rolling dice as they are
For this moment I am truly, really me!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Play dice!
Blah Blah... Nan ja kan ja... Ratty rat rat rat...
Blah Blah... This and that... Ratty rat rat rat...
Now let me recite to you the only thing that will hold true
YOLO is my ninja way, it's time to put those moves on display
Why stress about tomorrow when you've got today
Beyond the heart, 今はさ、行こうよ最高になんて誰も知らない
Beyond the heart, right now, let's go, nobody knows the absolute best
人生 総勢 忠誠、マジで、短あああい
Life, all, loyalty, it's seriously short!
One, and we see it as two, 負けてえぐい級
One, and we see it as two, losing is on a gross level
The rat's on the route, 花火、発射、まるで電波
The rat's on the route, fireworks, launch, just like radio waves
No math can settle this rat! Bae! No math can settle this rat! Bae!
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, and we just play dice.
Come and venture into my world upside down, nani nani no!
Time to run and follow us, won't stop till we're done
Idiots are allowed in infinite fun!
みんな自由じゃなきゃもったいないじゃん
It's a waste if everyone isn't free
It's time to light our change and just be bigger!
Don't you hesitate on what's ahead of you
That's the game or else you are screwed
泣いて笑い果てましょう、チュー、チュー、チュー
Let's cry and laugh to the end, chu, chu, chu
Baby, baby, it's a go!
Here we roll, here we cast, here we just Play Dice!
Baby, baby, there's no need to think twice.
Nani nani na-a-ah!
This is down, this is up, this is out for life.
Keep it coming, show them your best try!
後悔したならもう行きな-a-ah!
If you've got regrets, just go on already-a-ah!
What you doing bro, go out and live your life!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, PLAY DICE!
Now sing, baby!
何じゃかんじゃ
This and that
Ready, ra-ra-ra!
何じゃかんじゃ!
This and that!
Ah! Ah!
That was Play Dice! That was Play Dice, everyone!
Ah, I should probably get up. Whaaaa!
Finally! Hold on, give me a sec. Ahhh!
Finally, the long-awaited Play Dice!
I hope you guys liked that long-awaited
Play Dice performance.
Play Dice will always be my baby,
so I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Was it good?
How did the backups go? Oi, get out of here!
I'm protecting my backup dancers.
Anyway, but that was my first song, Play Dice.
Welcome to the performance section.
We're gonna keep on going. But for the next song,
I need a special... I need a... I need something else.
Hold on. I need a... I need a... I need this thing.
Oh, I need this thing.
Oh yes, I got the this thing. Okay.
So pretty much, the next song is a very special song
that I... I... I wanted to perform for you guys.
So I hope you enjoy. Next song I'm gonna sing is...
タイヨウのうた. Please listen.
Taiyou no Uta. Please listen.
タイヨウのうた
Taiyou no Uta
Lyrics / Composition: 白鳥マイカ
Lyrics / Composition: Shiratori Maika
震えている 私の手へ
Into my trembling hands,
初めて君が触れて
you touched me for the first time.
優しい気持ち 温かさに
To that kind feeling, that warmth,
やっと気づいたんだ
I finally realized.
閉ざした窓開ければ
If I open the closed window,
新しい風が吹いた
a new wind blows.
笑って 泣いて 君と出会えた
Laughing, crying, I was able to meet you.
見える世界は 輝き出した
The world I see has begun to shine.
ひまわり揺れる 太陽の下で
Sunflowers swaying under the sun,
感じていた
I was feeling
風を 君を
the wind, you...
信じること 迷うことも
Believing, wavering,
立ち止まることも
and even stopping...
全部 私が今ここで生きてる
Everything might be the answer
答えかもしれない
to why I'm living here now.
モノクロの毎日が
So that my monochrome days
色づいてゆくように
become filled with color.
笑って 泣いて 君と出会えた
Laughing, crying, I was able to meet you.
続く未来は 輝いていた
The future that follows was shining.
ひまわり揺れる 太陽の下で
Sunflowers swaying under the sun,
私のまま
as myself,
明日を 歌うよ
I will sing of tomorrow.
限りある日々を 止まらない時間（とき）を
In these finite days, throughout unstoppable time,
どれだけ愛せるかな?
How much can I love them?
愛せるよね 君がいれば
I can love them, as long as you're here.
光さえも そらさないで
Don't even look away from the light.
笑って 泣いて 君と出会えて
Laughing, crying, having met you...
続く未来は 輝いていた
The future that followed was shining.
ひまわり揺れる 太陽の下で
Under the sun where sunflowers sway,
私のまま 明日を
As myself, into tomorrow...
「ありがとう」伝えたい 今なら言えるよ
I want to say "thank you," I can say it now.
過ごした季節も 忘れはしないよ
I won't forget the seasons we spent together.
ひまわり揺れる 太陽のように
Like the sunflowers swaying in the sun,
私の歌 君を 照らすよ
My song will light your way.
私のまま
As myself,
君を...
You...
ラララ...
La la la...
Yeah!
Yay! Thank you so much for listening. That was Taiyou no Uta.
So for those who know, Taiyou no Uta is a very special song to me...
...because that was the very first song that I've ever learned.
The very first song that I ever learned how to play, how to sing by myself in a music room.
So I really hope you guys enjoyed it.
I'm getting emotional! Anyway, thank you so much. I hope you enjoyed it.
So, we're going to keep going!
Next song is also a very, very, very special and fun song...
...that I vowed I would perform one day, so I hope you guys enjoy.
Are you ready for the next song?
Third song: Ciki Ciki Bam Bam!
チキチキバンバン
Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
ちゃんちゃん あいちきちきばんばん
Chan chan, Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
あいちきちきばんばん
Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
ちゃんちゃん あいちきちきばんばん
Chan chan, Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
あいちきちきばんばん
Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
ちゃんちゃん あいちきちきばんばん
Chan chan, Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
猫も杓子も みんな気まぐれでツラい
Everyone and their mother, everyone's so fickle, it's tough
呼べばテキーラ あらぬ妄想 続（ぞく）でピカ
Calling out for Tequila, an ongoing delusion, sparkling
夢はパンドラ ほら開けたくなる
Dreams are Pandora's box, see, you'll want to open it
みんな期待して Party Tonight
Everyone's full of anticipation, Party Tonight
今夜フニャマ ノボロニャワカラナイ
Tonight, Funyama Roboronya, I don't know
合戦週末の宿命
The fate of the weekend battle
ちゃんちゃん あいちきちきばんばん
Chan chan, Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
何度ムシャクシャ したって Party Tonight
No matter how many times I'm irritated, Party Tonight
ちゃんちゃん あいちきちきばんばん
Chan chan, Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
愚か者ほど 背徳 ガズガズジャカ
The more foolish they are, the more immoral, Gazugazu-jaka
ちゃんちゃん あいちきちきばんばん
Chan chan, Ai Ciki Ciki Bam Bam
みんなスーパースターのタマゴさ Be With Tonight
Everyone's a superstar egg, Be With Tonight
Wow, such glamorous night!
でもも だけども みんな いらない Hands Up
But even so, we don't need any of them, Hands Up
Lili Neon Lili Night!
Japanese Beauty 密かに 今 沸騰
Japanese Beauty is secretly boiling now
Bounce the Vibe! Let's Shout it out!
飲めばドンドン...
If you drink, it goes on and on...
...行く　明けなきゃ伝説 yeah
...go, if it never ends it's a legend, yeah
Bam step, bam step, jump! 夢まき散らそう
Bam step, bam step, jump! Let's scatter dreams
夢まき散らそう
Let's scatter dreams
熱く dancing all yeah
Hot dancing all, yeah
太古の理想さ臆病蹴散らして
成り行き任せさ　ボン・ジョヴィなら
An ancient ideal, kicking away cowardice
Leave it to fate, if it's Bon Jovi
空は空は　空を飛ぶ絨毯
まさかさましても　向かないで
The sky is, the sky is, a flying carpet
Even if it's upside down, don't look back
イン気じゃダメ　韻踏むしたまい
誰々する前に　エンディング人生
Being gloomy is no good, go and rhyme
Before you're whoever, life's ending
見栄えのシャイニング輝度
はにか気にせず音量戦...
A good-looking shining brightness
Without worrying about shyness, volume war...
Oh baby, 降参不信ね　ハハハイセツキラー
Oh baby, a lack of surrender, ha ha high-sense killer
舞い高く舞い散りゃいいでしょ
燃え盛っちゃってもいいでしょ
It's fine to dance high and scatter
It's fine to even flare up
もう少しブレーキ　もう少し倍にゃ
暑くなるから危険は承知
Brake a little more, double it a little more
Knowing the danger as it gets hotter
ほらほら近い　スポットライトあてな
待ちわびた時だ　8時間!
Look, look, it's close, shine the spotlight
It's the long-awaited time, 8 hours!
チャンチャン! Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Chan chan! Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki chan chan
Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki chiki ban ban
Hai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki chan chan
Ai chiki chiki ban ban
愚か者ほどハイドロ加速さ　釈迦チャンチャン
The more foolish they are, the more hydro acceleration, Shaka chan chan
Ai chiki chiki ban ban
みんなずぶさまの卵たち忘れない
I won't forget everyone, those raw eggs
チャンチャン! Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Chan chan! Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki chan chan
Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki chiki ban ban
Hai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki chan chan
Ai chiki chiki ban ban
Ai chiki chiki!
Ha!
Thank you everyone!
That was Chiki Chiki Ban Ban!
I'm so glad that I was able to dance the dance
as well as sing the song.
I'm just so happy! Thank you!
Anyway, thank you so much for listening
to my third and... final song.
最後のお曲、あの、聞いてくれてありがとうございました!
Thank you for listening to my final song!
Anyway, yes, that was totally my final song.
But thank you so much for watching everyone!
It is time for the announcement time!
But to help me do this announcement,
I need a very special helper.
Hi! Helper please! I need help!
Squeakers, お疲れ様。お疲れ様です。
Squeakers, good job. Good job.
You're doing great. Boy Squeakers, you're doing great.
Thank you, Squeakers!
I present to you the Street Rat T-shirt!
Yes, this is my official 3D stream merch.
And yes, I have very little time to show this,
so we're on the clock, okay?
Street Rat T-Shirt
Okay, how fast can I do this? Shiotaru, here we go!
There are six key features of this t-shirt.
Six! Okay, let me sell it to you.
Number one, the logo on the front matches the one on the back.
Number two, there are stripes on the sleeves to make it really cool.
Number three, there are slits along the side to make it breathable and airable.
Number four, there are little distress details on the collar
because I got hungry and I decided to nibble a little bit.
Number five, there's a classic rat logo inside for you.
Number six, I designed this myself.
And yeah, oh, seven actually, there's a really cool design.
まあ、一応、日本語も少し。あの、まあ、グッズの紹介したと思います。
Well, for now, a little Japanese. Um, I think I've introduced the merch.
とてもかっこいいです。ぜひ買ってください。
It's very cool. Please buy it.
Please! Please buy it! It looks so cool! かっこいいでしょ？
Please! Please buy it! It looks so cool! It's cool, right?
그리고... 아... 한국어도 할게요. 아... 사주세요.
And... ah... I'll speak Korean too. Ah... please buy it.
멋있어요. 사주세요.
It's cool. Please buy it.
And the second announcement is that on October 9th, Council will be having their...
who's their? Our! 3D collab stream!
There'll be a lot of singing, games, and it's gonna be a lot of fun,
so I hope you guys come and watch that as well!
Well, I don't know guys, I feel like that's it.
これで終了？終わり？
Is that it? Is it over?
Is that it? I wonder... I don't know, they're telling me to go off stage.
Oh, we're going. That's it. We're gonna go now. Bye bye!
I had so much fun! I had so much fun!
I'll see you in the next show. I'll see you later. Okay, I'm coming! Bye bye!
Mr. Squeaks, come on, we gotta go. We gotta go.
アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Whoa, encore! What? I totally didn't expect this.
I mean, しょうがないよね。
I mean, it can't be helped, right?
Wow! Um, I guess we have time for one more encore song,
but before we head into the encore, I just wanted to say
thank you guys so much for watching. It's been absolutely incredible.
I wanted to thank everyone who helped with this, with this 3D celebration.
ダーマスさん本当にありがとうございます。
Damasu-san, thank you so very much.
And also my lovely, my lovely backup dancers as well.
Thank you, ありがとうございます。
Thank you, thank you very much.
And for the encore, if you know,
there's only one possible song that we would do for the encore.
Are you ready for the 3D?!
HERE WE GO!!
THE HERO!!〜怒れる拳に火をつけろ〜
Lyrics • Composition: 影山ヒロノブ
THE HERO!! ~Set Fire to the Angered Fist~
Lyrics • Composition: Hironobu Kageyama
ONE PUNCH!
3, 2, 1, Kill shot!
参上！必勝！史上最強！
Appearing! Certain victory! Strongest in history!
低空飛行！何者だ！？
Low-flying! Who is that!?
なんだかんだ言ったって最強
No matter what you say, he's the strongest,
ヒーローは俺だろ
the hero is me, right?
One Punch! 完了！連戦連勝！
One punch! Done! Victory after victory!
俺は勝つ！遂に勝つ！圧勝！
I'll win! I'll finally win! A complete victory!
Power! Get the power!
ギリギリ限界まで
To the very limits!
HERO! 俺を讃える声や
HERO! The voices praising me
喝采なんて欲しくはないさ
or the applause aren't what I want.
HERO! だから人知れず悪と戦う
HERO! So I fight evil in secret.
Nobody knows who he is.
空、覆い寄せる敵
The enemies closing in from the sky...
俺は背を向けはしないさ
I won't turn my back on them.
HERO! ならば揺るぎなき覚悟したため
HERO! If so, with unwavering resolve...
繰り出せ鉄拳
...unleash an iron fist!
3, 2, 1, Fight back!
参上！Go on! 正々堂々！
Appearing! Go on! Fair and square!
どうだこうだ言ったって何回も
No matter what you say, over and over,
守り抜くぜ！
I'll protect it all!
Justice! 執行！問答無用！
Justice! Executed! No questions asked!
俺が断つ！悪を断つ！断罪！
I'll sever it! Severing evil! Condemnation!
Power! Get the power!
アドレナリン溢れ出すぜ
Adrenaline is overflowing!
Power! Get the power!
鍛えた技をぶちかませ
Let loose the skills I've trained!
HERO! どんなに強い奴も
HERO! No matter how strong they are,
ちっぽけなガキだったんだ
they were just small kids once.
HERO! 弱き己乗り越え強くなる
HERO! Overcoming your weak self to become strong!
Nobody knows who he is.
神、宿る拳掲げて
Raising a fist where a god dwells...
俺は突き進むだけさ
I'll just keep pushing forward.
HERO! いつか敗北に汚泥舐めるまで
HERO! Until the day I taste the mud of defeat...
戦うヒーロー
...I'm a fighting hero!
俺は諦めない
I won't give up.
その胸に明日を描き
Drawing tomorrow in my heart,
目覚め行く世界へ今
into the awakening world now...
舞い上がれ強く高く
...soar up high and strong!
どんな時でも
No matter when,
何があっても
no matter what happens!
Put your hands up!
HERO! 俺を讃える声や
HERO! The voices praising me
喝采なんて欲しくはないさ
or the applause aren't what I want.
HERO! だから人知れず悪と戦う
HERO! So I fight evil in secret.
Nobody knows who he is.
神、宿る拳掲げて
Raising a fist where a god dwells...
俺は突き進むだけさ
I'll just keep pushing forward.
HERO! いつか敗北に汚泥舐めるまで
HERO! Until the day I taste the mud of defeat...
戦うヒーロー
...I'm a fighting hero!
孤独なヒーロー
A lonely hero!
I want to be a...
HERO!
Thank you everyone!
I'll see you next time!
Bye-bye!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Thank you for watching! This 3D showcase was only
possible because of you guys so from the bottom
of my heart, thank you ❤️ I love you guys so much!
-BAE-